# Mori Kenta

# **Full Stack Blockchain Developer**

Beyond guru

#### Introduction

## Solidity | Web3 | Cosmos Full-stack Developer

A seasoned results-driven blockchain & full-stack engineer. Always be hungry for learning new technology & improving myself, especially on blockchain scope. Have been developing lots of programing languages, frameworks, libraries, platforms, especially on JS/TS fields. Over the last 3 years, mainly focusing on blockchain technology, Solidity | Web3 | Ether | Cosmos SDK. Eagerto participate any DeFi, NFT mint, NFT marketplace & DApp firms and boost the project with my enthusiasm & experience. Now my focus is on the Cosmos SDK.

# Experience

### CosmosSDK Developer / Melechain Saudi Arab

From December 2021 to March 2022

Melechain is twin-coins ecosystem, private, enterprise-level blockchain.

- Developed liquidity pool for MELEG & MELEX
- Connect liquidity pool to Osmosis platform through Relayer Node using IBC
- Manage blockchain nodes/validators

# Web3 FE developer / Visor Finance United States

From May 2021 to November 2021

Worked on liquidity mining pool providing protocol with uniswapv3-core.

- Developed Governance Token with ERC20 & Hypervisor token with ERC721
- Introduced the React Saga and improve the performance
- Developed Crosswise exchange and optimize the responding time when switching network.

The biggest challenge was reducing the responding time after delegating unessential web3 calls and resolve the scalability with introducing theL2.

### Web3 | Plasma Sidechain | Ether Front-End developer / Privi Protocal

**United States** 

From October 2020 to June 2021

- Developed privi internal wallet
- Worked web3/ether on React/typescript based Front-End
- Introduced the Plasma side chain for creating private blockchain.
- Introduced the Polygon.

kenta.mori32@gmail.com

Osaka Japan

Date of birth 01/15/1992

#### Education

Osaka University in Japan Software Engineering

#### Skills

JS, TS, Python, Solidity, C, C#, Rust, Golang, Ruby, Node.js, React, Vue, Next, Nuxt, Angular, Laravel, Django, Flask, RoR, AWS, Heroku, React Native, Ionic, Flutter, GraphQL, SCSS, Ethereum, Truffle, Hardhat, Web3js, Etherjs, Cosmos, Solana-web3, DAO, Uniswap, Terra, Olympus Dao, Lending protocol, Curve Dao, etc.

#### Interests

Reading • Building Ideas • Designing • Psychology

# Experience

#### **BLOCKCHAIN DEVLOPER / TrueFi** United States

From February 2019 to May 2019

- Have developed Ethereum Smart Energy contract and react Front-end with react, web3, ether.js
- Developed Anoswap using React Saga and improve the performance
- Introduce the embedded signature wallet on existing system.

### FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER / Smooth Team United States

From May 2017 to October 2018

- Developed web and database applications to assist with daily business processes for customers and internal team.
- Designed and guided the implementation of corporate-wide customer solutions. Collaborated with Value Added Resellers and Independent Software Vendors to develop and close opportunities.